Contact

gagan Delhi road, Moradabad anuj.123mbd@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anuj-gaurav-9b9195217 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Operating Systems

Data Structures

Anuj Gaurav

INTERN AT SUVIDHA FOUNDATION (WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT) || C || C++ || PYTHON || FRONTEND DEVELOPER || UI/UX || MY SQL || DATA STRUCTURE || GITHUB || FIGMA

Moradabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

Summary

Experienced Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the e-learning industry. Skilled in Communication, English, Time Management, Leadership, and Engineering. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University.

Experience

Suvidha Foundation 3 months

Frontend Developer
January 2022 - March 2022 (3 months)
Work from home

Student Intern January 2022 - March 2022 (3 months) Work from home

Education

Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (August 2020 - November 2024)